<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LingoE</string>
    <string name="lets_learn_english">Let\'s Learn English!</string>
    <string name="get_to_know_the_english_writing">Get to know the English grammar</string>
    <string name="system">system...</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="happy_alphabets">Happy Alphabets</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>

    <string name="oops">Oops…!</string>
    <string name="the_content_is_being_prepared...">The content is being prepared…</string>
    <string name="happy_books">Happy Books</string>
    <string name="read_these_english_short_books">Read these English short books</string>
    <string name="and_be_good_at_reading">and be good at reading...</string>
    <string name="app_title">Title of the article</string>
    <string name="app_description">This is the description of the article and whenever I wanna change it I can because its a good way of creating strings.</string>


    <string name="article_one_title">5 SIMPLE WAYS TO IMPROVE YOUR WRITTEN ENGLISH</string>

    <string name="article_one_description">Many people struggle with writing in English and it can seem like a real challenge to improve. Don’t
        worry, though. Here are some simple steps that you can take to improve your written English and
        impress people with your writing skills.
    \n\n1. Expand your vocabulary.
        \n\nTo express yourself clearly, you need a good active vocabulary. That’s not just being able to
        recognise lots of words – it means actually being able to use them correctly. Do this by learning
        new words with example sentences, not just word lists.
    \n\n2. Master English spelling.
        \n\nYou must know how to spell those words correctly. Incorrect spelling changes the meaning of your
        sentence. For example: ‘bare’ and ‘bear’ sound the same but ‘bare’ means naked and ‘bear’ is a
        large animal. Additionally, incorrect spelling makes it difficult for the reader to understand what
        you’ve written.
    \n\n3. Read regularly.
        \n\nPeople often say that we learn to write best by reading. Reading in English is useful in many ways
        It is a great way to get an idea of the different styles of writing and see how to use words
        appropriately.
    \n\n4. Improve your grammar.
        \n\nGrammar is very important because it improves the quality of your writing. Always use the
        appropriate tense and remember to use punctuation. Punctuation is a great way to make your
        writing clear and fluent.
    \n\n5. Just do it!
        \n\nWriting can be daunting. However, the best way to improve is get a pen and paper or sit in front of
        your computer and actually write. Be prepared to write several versions of each text because even
        for professional writers, the first draft is never perfect. Remember, practice makes perfect, so now
        is the best time to sit down and get started with our the English quizzes!</string>


    <string name="article_two_title">IMPROVE WRITING SKILLS DRAMATICALLY BY DOING THESE 15 THINGS</string>

    <string name="article_two_description">Learning a variety of tricks to improve writing skills isn’t as difficult as you may think.
        We’ve put together a list of steps to help you make dramatic improvements to the
        quality of your writing in short order.
        \nBecoming a better writer takes practice, and you’re already practicing. No, seriously
        —you write a lot. Even if you don’t think of yourself as a writer, you put thoughts into
        text more often than you realize. At the very least, you write emails—a lot of emails
        —post on social media, make updates to your résumé and LinkedIn profile, and
        message your friends. If your job requires it, you also create things like reports,
        presentations, newsletters . . . it’s a long list.
        So, you’re already writing. Now, to improve writing is just a matter of becoming
        conscious of the things you can do to give your text more structure and make your
        copy crisp and readable with a conversational style.
    \n\nGive Your Writing Structure.
        \n\nIt’s fine to rattle off a stream of consciousness when you’re writing in your journal,
        but if you actually want to communicate with others you’ll need to bring some order
        to those rambling thoughts. Here are some tips.
    \n\n1. Make sure you’re clear on the concepts you’re writing about.
        \n\nAlbert Einstein said, “If you can’t explain it to a six-year-old, you don’t understand it
        yourself.” Before you start writing, take a moment to mentally explain the concept to
        the six-year-old who lives inside your head. (We all have one, don’t we?) If your writing
        goal is to achieve a specific result, ask yourself what that result should be. Before
        you dive into writing, have a clear purpose. Then stick to it.
    \n\n2. If the message is complex, outline it.
        \n\nIt doesn’t take much thought-organizing to compose the average text message, but if
        you’re writing something more complex, with multiple angles, questions, or requests,
        get all that stuff sorted before you sit down to write. Making an outline, or even just
        some quick notes about the topics you want to cover, can save you time answering
        clarifying questions later. And speaking of questions . . .
    \n\n3. Anticipate your readers’ questions.
        \n\nImproving writing involves putting yourself in your readers’ shoes. Do they have
        enough context to understand what you’ve written for them? If not, fill in the blanks.
        But . . .
    \n\n4. Don’t over-explain everything.
        \n\nIf you’ve taken the time to organize your thoughts in advance, you should be able to
        keep things simple. The idea is to give readers just enough to understand what you’re
        communicating without overwhelming them with trivial details. If you find yourself
        getting in the weeds with more details than you need, look at each piece of
        information and ask whether it’s essential to help your reader understand your
        message. If not, get rid of it.
    \n\n5. Go easy on the prepositional phrases.
        \n\nWhen I was a neophyte writer, someone showed me how prepositional phrases made
        my writing unnecessarily wordy and complex. It was an epiphany!
        Prepositions aren’t difficult to understand, but the concept does require some
        explanation. Get smart about prepositions here, and then try to simplify them
        whenever it makes sense. Your writing will get a much-needed clarity boost.
    \n\n6. Eliminate the filler words and phrases.
        \n\nSome words show up in our writing all the time, and yet they don’t contribute much of
        anything. Although these filler words and phrases sometimes add color or even
        meaning, most of the time they contribute nothing but clutter. Here are thirty-one of
        them you can eliminate right now.
    \n\n7. Don’t pad weak words with adverbs.
        \n\nAdverbs—those words that often end in -ly—modify verbs and sometimes
        adjectives. They’re okay once in a while, but when you find yourself using them all the
        time, you’re probably making weak word choices. Instead of “ran really fast” write
        “sprinted.” Was something “extremely funny”? Nah, it was “hilarious.” The scenery
        may have been “very beautiful,” but your writing’s going to shine if you refer to it as
        “gorgeous,” “lush,” “verdant,” or “bucolic.”
    \n\n8. Stick with simple words.
        \n\nBestselling author John Grisham said, “There are three types of words: (1) words we
        know; (2) words we should know; (3) words nobody knows. Forget those in the third
        category and use restraint with those in the second.” There’s a difference between
        having a rich vocabulary and dropping million-dollar words into your writing just to
        show off. Unless it’s your intent to be poetic, keep your language simple and direct.
    \n\n9. Use contractions.
        \n\nEnglish speakers use contractions—you’re, I’m, we’re, they’re, can’t, didn’t. Your
        writing will sound stiff and formal without them.
    \n\n10. Try transcribing yourself.
        \n\nRecord yourself talking. You can learn a lot about conversational writing using this
        one weird trick! (Sorry, Buzzfeed, we tease because we care.)
        Try transcribing a conversation you’ve recorded (with the other person’s permission,
        of course). Transcribe a couple of minutes of the conversation word-for-word. Then,
        fix or remove any false starts and remove filler (um, uh, like, you know)—et voila!—
        you’ve got yourself some conversational writing. The process of transcribing and
        editing will help you learn what to do and what not to.
    \n\n11. Throw away the grammar rule book . . . within reason.
        \n\nWe, the Grammarly team, give you permission to start sentences with conjunctions.
        And (see what we did there?) unless you’re writing something formal, we’re perfectly
        okay with you ending some sentences with prepositions. Write naturally, human! It’s
        all good.
    \n\n12.  Keep your sentences simple.
        \n\nLiterary greats can write long, complex sentences with flair. Why not you? Well, for
        starters you’re probably not trying to write like Tolstoy, Nabokov, or Faulkner. Short,
        less complicated sentences are easier to read. Keep it simple, silly! But do vary your
        sentence length so your writing has a nice flow.
    \n\n13. Read it out loud.
        \n\nSpeaking of flow, reading your writing aloud can help you determine whether it flows
        smoothly. If it sounds choppy and clipped, add a few longer sentences to break up
        that steady, monotonous beat. If you find yourself stumbling over parts, you’ve
        probably found an overly complex sentence that needs rewriting. I always
        recommend reading your work out loud . . . because it works!
    \n\n14. Infuse your personality into your writing.
        \n\nLetting your personality shine through is the best way to develop a writing style. Use
        the phrases and slang that you would normally use (within reason). When it’s
        appropriate, throw in a relevant personal anecdote. In all but the most formal or
        professional writing settings, be yourself when you write.
    \n\n15. Practice, practice, practice!
        \n\nThe ultimate way to improving writing is to learn what weakens it in the first place,
        and then set your mind to fixing (and eventually preventing) the glitches. The more
        you write, edit, and proofread, the better you get at it. </string>


    <string name="article_three_title">10 TOP TIPS FOR IMPROVING YOUR SPOKEN ENGLISH</string>

    <string name="article_three_description">Practising speaking is one of the most fun and rewarding parts of learning English. Once you can
        speak even a little English, there are loads of ways to improve your skills quickly while having tons
        of fun. Here are ten top tips for improving your spoken English and having a great time while you do it!
    \n\n1. Speak, speak, speak!
        \n\nBe confident and speak as often as possible to as many people as you possibly can! Do not be shy
        to make mistakes! The more you practice the better and more confident you will become in your
        pronunciation and vocabulary. Remember, speaking is a skill like learning a musical instrument or
        new sport – the only way you can get good is to actually do it!
    \n\n2. Use technology.
        \n\nA smartphone can be a powerful tool for learning languages. Use it to record yourself speaking
        then listen back to see how your English sounds to other people. Make the most of all your
        favourite productivity apps to organise your practice time and make a note of all the new words
        you learn.
    \n\n3. Listen.
        \n\nListen to news bulletins and songs in English to listen to the pronunciation of words. You can also
        learn new words and expressions this way. The more you listen, the more you learn! Try copying
        what you hear to practise your pronunciation and learn which words in a sentence are stressed.
    \n\n4. Read out loud.
        \n\nRead the newspaper or a magazine out to yourself. You could even find a script for your favourite
        TV show and act it out! This is a great way to practise pronunciation because you only need to
        concentrate on making sure you English sounds great and don’t need to worry about sentence
        structure or grammar.
    \n\n5. Learn a new word every day.
        \n\nChoose a word you would like to work on and use practice it in different sentences. Use the word
        until you have learnt it and keep using it regularly.
    \n\n6. Watch films.
        \n\nWatch movies in English and pay attention to new vocabulary and pronunciation.
        Imitate the actors and have fun with it
    \n\n7. Make friends.
        \n\nMake friends with English speakers or others learning to speak English and compare notes. Talk
        about things that you have learnt and exchange ideas.
    \n\n8. Do interesting activities in English.
        \n\nTake a cooking course in English or join a book club! Anything you enjoy doing, make sure you do it
        and communicate it in English. Using English to talk about things you enjoy will make practising a
        positive experience.
    \n\n9. Have a debate.
        \n\nDebate all the topics that interest you with friends in English. Try to use as much vocabulary as you
        can to get your point across and listen to the other arguments carefully so you can argue against
        them effectively.
    \n\n10. Use a dictionary.
        \n\nOnline dictionaries often have audio examples so you can check your pronunciation and there are
        lots of great dictionary apps that you can take everywhere with you on your smartphone. Make
        sure not to become too reliant on these tools, though. Have a go at saying the words first then
        check afterwards to see if you were right!
        \n\nSo, with all these practice tips to choose from, which one are you going to try first?</string>
</resources>